Guide to the William Leonard Albrecht Papers 1880-1968
Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, The University of Montana--Missoula
William Leonard Albrecht Papers
1880-1968
University of Montana, Mansfield Library, Archives and Special Collections The University of Montana—Missoula Missoula, MT 59812 406-243-2053 http://www.lib.umt.edu/asc library.archives@umontana.edu
Mss 050
Albrecht, William Leonard, 1863-1935
71.0 linear feet 85 boxes, 3 oversize tubes, and 127 oversize volumes
This collection contains correspondence, financial, legal, organizational, promotional, and photographic records generated or collected by William Leonard Albrecht with particular emphasis on the Albrecht Furniture Company, the first and one of the most distinguished furniture stores in Great Falls, Montana.
Biographical Note
William Leonard Albrecht was born in 1863 in Rothenburg, Germany, the son of Frederick A. and Sophia (Schmidt) Albrecht. He emigrated to the United States in 1882 and began working in Detroit, Michigan, as a bookkeeper. After six months there, he moved on to Minneapolis, where he worked for a firm that manufactured billiard tables and bank furniture. He left that firm and traveled throughout the Northwest looking for a location to start a business. In 1886 he arrived in Great Falls, Montana, where he opened the city's first furniture store.
In 1887, he built the brick building that would house the store for the next eighty-one years. Albrecht's Furniture sold a whole variety of furnishings for the home. The store often struggled with varying financial conditions, but stayed in business at 111 Central Avenue East until 1968.
Albrecht was active in other business concerns as well. He was a director, vice president, and president of the Gold Black Sand Mining Company, which was headquartered in Great Falls. He was also active in the German-American community, and was a member of the Sons of Hermann (which published the Montana Herold, a German newspaper, out of Great Falls from 1892 to 1898) and the German Lodge of Great Falls. He was a minor stockholder in the Cascade and Bitter Root Lumber Company.
Albrecht married Wilhelmine Loeffler in Chicago in 1894. They had three children: William Jr., Helmuth, and Elsie. William Sr. died in 1935; William Jr. owned and managed the store until its closure in 1968; he died in 1975.
This collection contains correspondence, financial, legal, organizational, promotional, and photographic records generated or collected by William Leonard Albrecht with particular emphasis on the Albrecht Furniture Company, the first and one of the most distinguished furniture stores in Great Falls, Montana. Collection materials also include limited records from some of the Albrecht family's other investments, the Gold Black Sand Mining Company, the Montana Herold Publishing Company, and the Cascade and Bitter Root Lumber Company. This collection provides particular insights into the history and practices of home furnishing businesses in central Montana from the late 19th Century through the mid 20th century. Correspondence materials include personal exchanges with members of the extended Albrecht family. This correspondence, in conjunction with the Sons of Hermann materials, provides insights into German immigrant experiences and perspectives during Montana's pioneer-era. Additionally, collection materials document the challenges of establishing retail businesses in a rural state.
The collection is arranged in six series:
Series I: Albrecht Furniture Company
Subseries 1: Incoming Correspondence
Subseries 2: Interoffice Correspondence
Subseries 3: Outgoing Correspondence
Subseries 4: General Correspondence
Subseries 5: Financial Records
Subseries 6: Legal Documents
Subseries 7: Advertising and Organizational
Series II: Gold Black Sand Mining Company
Subseries 1: General Correspondence
Subseries 2: Legal and Organizational
Subseries 3: Clippings
Series III: Sons of Hermann, Bismarck Lodge No. 1
Subseries 1: Financial Records
Subseries 2: Montana Herold Publishing Company
Series IV: German Lodge, Great Falls
Series V: Cascade and Bitter Root Lumber Company
Series VI: Photographs
Researchers must use collection in accordance with the policies of Archives and Special Collections, the Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, and the University of Montana--Missoula.
The records were held by the Albrecht family until time of donation.
Gift of Helmuth Albrecht and Elsa Albrecht, 1972.
During original processing, German-language books were removed from the collection and placed in the Mansfield Library's general collection.
This collection is indexed under the following headings in the online catalog. Researchers desiring materials about related topics, persons, or places should search the catalog using these headings.
Albrecht Furniture Company (Great Falls, Mont.); Montana Herold Publishing Company; Cascade and Bitter Root Lumber Company; Gold Black Sand Mining Company; German Lodge (Great Falls, Mont.); Order of the Sons of Hermann
Furniture industry and trade--Montana--Great Falls; German American newspapers--Montana--Great Falls; German Americans--Montana--Great Falls; German Americans--Montana--Great Falls--Societies, etc.; Lumber trade--Montana--Great Falls; Mining corporations--Montana--Great Falls; Newspaper publishing--Montana--Great Falls
Business records--Montana--Great Falls
Montana; Business, Industry, and Labor; German Americans; Logging; Mines and Mineral Resources
Businessmen--Montana--Great Falls
Montana Herold
- Albrecht Furniture Company, 1886-1968; Series I; 47.25 linear feet, 113 oversize volumes, and 3 oversize tubes
  This series contains extensive correspondence, financial, legal, organizational, and promotional materials generated and collected by the Albrecht family with particular emphasis upon the operation of the Albrecht Furniture Company in Great Falls, Montana. These materials provide insights into the history and practices of home furnishing businesses in central Montana from the late 19th century through the mid-20th century. Correspondence materials also include personal exchanges with members of the extended Albrecht family, documenting aspects of German immigrant experiences and perspectives during Montana's pioneer-era. Additionally these items document the challenges of establishing retail businesses in a rural state.
  - Incoming Correspondence, 1897-1934; Subseries 1; 5.25 linear feet
    - 1897 (Box-folder 1/1)
    - 1906 (Box-folder 1/2)
    - 1907 (Box-folder 1/3)
    - A, 1908 (Box-folder 1/4)
    - B, 1908 (Box-folder 1/5)
    - C, 1908 (Box-folder 1/6)
    - D, 1908 (Box-folder 1/7)
    - E, 1908 (Box-folder 1/8)
    - F, 1908 (Box-folder 1/9)
    - G, 1908 (Box-folder 1/10)
    - H, 1908 (Box-folder 1/11)
    - J, 1908 (Box-folder 1/12)
    - K, 1908 (Box-folder 1/13)
    - L, 1908 (Box-folder 1/14)
    - M, 1908 (Box-folder 1/15)
    - N, 1908 (Box-folder 1/16)
    - O, 1908 (Box-folder 1/17)
    - P, 1908 (Box-folder 1/18)
    - R, 1908 (Box-folder 1/19)
    - S, 1908 (Box-folder 1/20)
    - T, 1908 (Box-folder 1/21)
    - U, 1908 (Box-folder 1/22)
    - V, 1908 (Box-folder 1/23)
    - W, 1908 (Box-folder 1/24)
    - Z, 1908 (Box-folder 1/25)
    - A, 1914 (Box-folder 1/26)
    - B, 1914 (Box-folder 1/27)
    - C, 1914 (Box-folder 1/28)
    - D, 1914 (Box-folder 1/29)
    - E, 1914 (Box-folder 1/30)
    - F, 1914 (Box-folder 2/1)
    - G, 1914 (Box-folder 2/2)
    - H, 1914 (Box-folder 2/3)
    - J, 1914 (Box-folder 2/4)
    - K, 1914 (Box-folder 2/5)
    - L, 1914 (Box-folder 2/6)
    - M, 1914 (Box-folder 2/7)
    - N, 1914 (Box-folder 2/8)
    - O, 1914 (Box-folder 2/9)
    - P, 1914 (Box-folder 2/10)
    - Q, 1914 (Box-folder 2/11)
    - R, 1914 (Box-folder 2/12)
    - S, 1914 (Box-folder 2/13)
    - T, 1914 (Box-folder 2/14)
    - U, 1914 (Box-folder 2/15)
    - V, 1914 (Box-folder 2/16)
    - W, 1914 (Box-folder 2/17)
    - Y, 1914 (Box-folder 2/18)
    - Z, 1914 (Box-folder 2/19)
    - C, 1916 (Box-folder 2/20)
    - K, 1916 (Box-folder 2/21)
    - A, 1917 (Box-folder 2/22)
    - B, 1917 (Box-folder 2/23)
    - C, 1917 (Box-folder 2/24)
    - D, 1917 (Box-folder 2/25)
    - E, 1917 (Box-folder 2/26)
    - G, 1917 (Box-folder 2/27)
    - H, 1917 (Box-folder 2/28)
    - I, 1917 (Box-folder 3/1)
    - J, 1917 (Box-folder 3/2)
    - K, 1917 (Box-folder 3/3)
    - L, 1917 (Box-folder 3/4)
    - M, 1917 (Box-folder 3/5)
    - N, 1917 (Box-folder 3/6)
    - O, 1917 (Box-folder 3/7)
    - P, 1917 (Box-folder 3/8)
    - A, 1918 (Box-folder 3/9)
    - B, 1918 (Box-folder 3/10)
    - C, 1918 (Box-folder 3/11)
    - D, 1918 (Box-folder 3/12)
    - F, 1918 (Box-folder 3/13)
    - G, 1918 (Box-folder 3/14)
    - H, 1918 (Box-folder 3/15)
    - I, 1918 (Box-folder 3/16)
    - J, 1918 (Box-folder 3/17)
    - K, 1918 (Box-folder 3/18)
    - L, 1918 (Box-folder 3/19)
    - M, 1918 (Box-folder 3/20)
    - N, 1918 (Box-folder 3/21)
    - O, 1918 (Box-folder 3/22)
    - P, 1918 (Box-folder 3/23)
    - A, 1919 (Box-folder 3/24)
    - B, 1919 (Box-folder 3/25)
    - C, 1919 (Box-folder 3/26)
    - D, 1919 (Box-folder 3/27)
    - E, 1919 (Box-folder 3/28)
    - F, 1919 (Box-folder 3/29)
    - G, 1919 (Box-folder 3/30)
    - H, 1919 (Box-folder 4/1)
    - I, 1919 (Box-folder 4/2)
    - J, 1919 (Box-folder 4/3)
    - K, 1919 (Box-folder 4/4)
    - L, 1919 (Box-folder 4/5)
    - M, 1919 (Box-folder 4/6)
    - N, 1919 (Box-folder 4/7)
    - O, 1919 (Box-folder 4/8)
    - P, 1919 (Box-folder 4/9)
    - Q, 1919 (Box-folder 4/10)
    - R, 1919 (Box-folder 4/11)
    - S, 1919 (Box-folder 4/12)
    - T, 1919 (Box-folder 4/13)
    - U, 1919 (Box-folder 4/14)
    - V, 1919 (Box-folder 4/15)
    - W, 1919 (Box-folder 4/16)
    - Y, 1919 (Box-folder 4/17)
    - A, 1920 (Box-folder 4/18)
    - B, 1920 (Box-folder 4/19)
    - C, 1920 (Box-folder 4/20)
    - D, 1920 (Box-folder 4/21)
    - E, 1920 (Box-folder 4/22)
    - F, 1920 (Box-folder 4/23)
    - G, 1920 (Box-folder 4/24)
    - H, 1920 (Box-folder 4/25)
    - J, 1920 (Box-folder 5/1)
    - K, 1920 (Box-folder 5/2)
    - L, 1920 (Box-folder 5/3)
    - M, 1920 (Box-folder 5/4)
    - N, 1920 (Box-folder 5/5)
    - O, 1920 (Box-folder 5/6)
    - P, 1920 (Box-folder 5/7)
    - R, 1920 (Box-folder 5/8)
    - S, 1920 (Box-folder 5/9)
    - T, 1920 (Box-folder 5/10)
    - U, 1920 (Box-folder 5/11)
    - V, 1920 (Box-folder 5/12)
    - W, 1920 (Box-folder 5/13)
    - Y, 1920 (Box-folder 5/14)
    - Z, 1920 (Box-folder 5/15)
    - C, 1923 (Box-folder 5/16)
    - T, 1926 (Box-folder 5/17)
    - C, 1927 (Box-folder 5/18)
    - N, 1927 (Box-folder 5/19)
    - R, 1927 (Box-folder 5/20)
    - S, 1927 (Box-folder 5/21)
    - T, 1927 (Box-folder 5/22)
    - A, 1928 (Box-folder 5/23)
    - B, 1928 (Box-folder 5/24)
    - C, 1928 (Box-folder 5/25)
    - D, 1928 (Box-folder 5/26)
    - E, 1928 (Box-folder 5/27)
    - F, 1928 (Box-folder 5/28)
    - G, 1928 (Box-folder 5/29)
    - H, 1928 (Box-folder 5/30)
    - I, 1928 (Box-folder 5/31)
    - J, 1928 (Box-folder 5/32)
    - K, 1928 (Box-folder 5/33)
    - L, 1928 (Box-folder 5/34)
    - M, 1928 (Box-folder 5/35)
    - N, 1928 (Box-folder 6/1)
    - O, 1928 (Box-folder 6/2)
    - R, 1928 (Box-folder 6/3)
    - S, 1928 (Box-folder 6/4)
    - T, 1928 (Box-folder 6/5)
    - U, 1928 (Box-folder 6/6)
    - V, 1928 (Box-folder 6/7)
    - W, 1928 (Box-folder 6/8)
    - A, 1929 (Box-folder 6/9)
    - B, 1929 (Box-folder 6/10)
    - C, 1929 (Box-folder 6/11)
    - D, 1929 (Box-folder 6/12)
    - E, 1929 (Box-folder 6/13)
    - F, 1929 (Box-folder 6/14)
    - G, 1929 (Box-folder 6/15)
    - H, 1929 (Box-folder 6/16)
    - J, 1929 (Box-folder 6/17)
    - K, 1929 (Box-folder 6/18)
    - L, 1929 (Box-folder 6/19)
    - M, 1929 (Box-folder 6/20)
    - N, 1929 (Box-folder 6/21)
    - O, 1929 (Box-folder 6/22)
    - R, 1929 (Box-folder 6/23)
    - S, 1929 (Box-folder 6/24)
    - T, 1929 (Box-folder 6/25)
    - U, 1929 (Box-folder 6/26)
    - V, 1929 (Box-folder 6/27)
    - W, 1929 (Box-folder 6/28)
    - Y, 1929 (Box-folder 6/29)
    - A, 1930 (Box-folder 7/1)
    - B, 1930 (Box-folder 7/2)
    - C, 1930 (Box-folder 7/3)
    - D, 1930 (Box-folder 7/4)
    - E, 1930 (Box-folder 7/5)
    - F, 1930 (Box-folder 7/6)
    - G, 1930 (Box-folder 7/7)
    - H, 1930 (Box-folder 7/8)
    - I, 1930 (Box-folder 7/9)
    - J, 1930 (Box-folder 7/10)
    - K, 1930 (Box-folder 7/11)
    - L, 1930 (Box-folder 7/12)
    - M, 1930 (Box-folder 7/13)
    - N, 1930 (Box-folder 7/14)
    - O, 1930 (Box-folder 7/15)
    - P, 1930 (Box-folder 7/16)
    - Q, 1930 (Box-folder 7/17)
    - R, 1930 (Box-folder 7/18)
    - S, 1930 (Box-folder 7/19)
    - T, 1930 (Box-folder 7/20)
    - U, 1930 (Box-folder 7/21)
    - V, 1930 (Box-folder 7/22)
    - W, 1930 (Box-folder 7/23)
    - Y, 1930 (Box-folder 7/24)
    - A, 1931 (Box-folder 7/25)
    - B, 1931 (Box-folder 7/26)
    - C, 1931 (Box-folder 7/27)
    - D, 1931 (Box-folder 7/28)
    - E, 1931 (Box-folder 7/29)
    - F, 1931 (Box-folder 7/30)
    - G, 1931 (Box-folder 7/31)
    - H, 1931 (Box-folder 8/1)
    - I, 1931 (Box-folder 8/2)
    - J, 1931 (Box-folder 8/3)
    - K, 1931 (Box-folder 8/4)
    - L, 1931 (Box-folder 8/5)
    - M, 1931 (Box-folder 8/6)
    - N, 1931 (Box-folder 8/7)
    - O, 1931 (Box-folder 8/8)
    - R, 1931 (Box-folder 8/9)
    - S, 1931 (Box-folder 8/10)
    - T, 1931 (Box-folder 8/11)
    - U, 1931 (Box-folder 8/12)
    - V, 1931 (Box-folder 8/13)
    - W, 1931 (Box-folder 8/14)
    - Y, 1931 (Box-folder 8/15)
    - A, 1932 (Box-folder 8/16)
    - B, 1932 (Box-folder 8/17)
    - C, 1932 (Box-folder 8/18)
    - D, 1932 (Box-folder 8/19)
    - E, 1932 (Box-folder 8/20)
    - F, 1932 (Box-folder 8/21)
    - G, 1932 (Box-folder 8/22)
    - H, 1932 (Box-folder 8/23)
    - I, 1932 (Box-folder 8/24)
    - J, 1932 (Box-folder 8/25)
    - K, 1932 (Box-folder 8/26)
    - L, 1932 (Box-folder 8/27)
    - M, 1932 (Box-folder 8/28)
    - N, 1932 (Box-folder 8/29)
    - O, 1932 (Box-folder 8/30)
    - R, 1932 (Box-folder 8/31)
    - S, 1932 (Box-folder 8/32)
    - T, 1932 (Box-folder 8/33)
    - U, 1932 (Box-folder 9/1)
    - V, 1932 (Box-folder 9/2)
    - W, 1932 (Box-folder 9/3)
    - Y, 1932 (Box-folder 9/4)
    - A, 1933 (Box-folder 9/5)
    - B, 1933 (Box-folder 9/6)
    - C, 1933 (Box-folder 9/7)
    - D, 1933 (Box-folder 9/8)
    - E, 1933 (Box-folder 9/9)
    - F, 1933 (Box-folder 9/10)
    - G, 1933 (Box-folder 9/11)
    - H, 1933 (Box-folder 9/12)
    - I, 1933 (Box-folder 9/13)
    - K, 1933 (Box-folder 9/14)
    - L, 1933 (Box-folder 9/15)
    - M, 1933 (Box-folder 9/16)
    - N, 1933 (Box-folder 9/17)
    - R, 1933 (Box-folder 9/18)
    - S, 1933 (Box-folder 9/19)
    - T, 1933 (Box-folder 9/20)
    - U, 1933 (Box-folder 9/21)
    - V, 1933 (Box-folder 9/22)
    - W, 1933 (Box-folder 9/23)
    - Y, 1933 (Box-folder 9/24)
    - A, 1934 (Box-folder 9/25)
    - B, 1934 (Box-folder 9/26)
    - C, 1934 (Box-folder 9/27)
    - D, 1934 (Box-folder 10/1)
    - E, 1934 (Box-folder 10/2)
    - F, 1934 (Box-folder 10/3)
    - G, 1934 (Box-folder 10/4)
    - H, 1934 (Box-folder 10/5)
    - I, 1934 (Box-folder 10/6)
    - J, 1934 (Box-folder 10/7)
    - K, 1934 (Box-folder 10/8)
    - L, 1934 (Box-folder 10/9)
    - M, 1934 (Box-folder 10/10)
    - N, 1934 (Box-folder 10/11)
    - O, 1934 (Box-folder 10/12)
    - P, 1934 (Box-folder 10/13)
    - R, 1934 (Box-folder 10/14)
    - S, 1934 (Box-folder 10/15)
    - T, 1934 (Box-folder 10/16)
    - U, 1934 (Box-folder 10/17)
    - V, 1934 (Box-folder 10/18)
    - W, 1934 (Box-folder 10/19)
    - Y, 1934 (Box-folder 10/20)
  - Interoffice Correspondence, 1936; Subseries 2; 1 folder
    - 1936 (Box-folder 10/21)
  - Outgoing Correspondence, 1886-1965; Subseries 3; 6.25 linear feet
    - October 1886-November1890 (Box-folder 10/22)
    - December 1890-March 1899 (Box-folder 11/1)
    - March 1899-July 1900 (Box-folder 11/2)
    - July 1900-August 1901 (Box-folder 11/3)
    - August 1901-March 1903 (Box-folder 12/1)
    - March 1903-June 1905 (Box-folder 12/2)
    - July 1905-July 1907 (Box-folder 12/3)
    - July 1907-February 1909 (Box-folder 12/4)
    - February 1909-August 1910 (Box-folder 13/1)
    - August 1910-June 1912 (Box-folder 13/2)
    - June 1912-October 1913 (Box-folder 13/3)
    - October 1913-March 1914 (Box-folder 13/4)
    - March-April 1914 (Box-folder 14/1)
    - May-July 1914 (Box-folder 14/2)
    - August-October 1914 (Box-folder 14/3)
    - November-December 1914 (Box-folder 14/4)
    - January-May 1915 (Box-folder 14/5)
    - June-September 1915 (Box-folder 14/6)
    - October-December 1915 (Box-folder 14/7)
    - 1916 (Box-folder 14/8)
    - 1917 (Box-folder 14/9)
    - 1918 (Box-folder 14/10)
    - January-April 1935 (Box-folder 15/1)
    - May-December 1935 (Box-folder 15/2)
    - January-May 1936 (Box-folder 15/3)
    - June-October 1936 (Box-folder 15/4)
    - October-December 1936 (Box-folder 15/5)
    - January-May 1937 (Box-folder 15/6)
    - June-August 1937 (Box-folder 15/7)
    - September-October 1937 (Box-folder 15/8)
    - November-December 1937 (Box-folder 15/9)
    - January-March 1938 (Box-folder 15/10)
    - April-June 1938 (Box-folder 15/11)
    - July-October 1938 (Box-folder 16/1)
    - November-December 1938 (Box-folder 16/2)
    - January-March 1939 (Box-folder 16/3)
    - April-June 1939 (Box-folder 16/4)
    - July-September 1939 (Box-folder 16/5)
    - October-November 1939 (Box-folder 16/6)
    - December 1939 (Box-folder 16/7)
    - January-February 1940 (Box-folder 16/8)
    - March 1940 (Box-folder 16/9)
    - April 1940 (Box-folder 16/10)
    - May 1940 (Box-folder 16/11)
    - June-July 1940 (Box-folder 16/12)
    - August-September 1940 (Box-folder 16/13)
    - October-December 1940 (Box-folder 16/14)
    - January-March 1941 (Box-folder 17/1)
    - April-July 1941 (Box-folder 17/2)
    - August-September 1941 (Box-folder 17/3)
    - October-December 1941 (Box-folder 17/4)
    - January-April 1942 (Box-folder 17/5)
    - May-August 1942 (Box-folder 17/6)
    - September-December 1942 (Box-folder 17/7)
    - 1943 (Box-folder 17/8)
    - 1944 (Box-folder 17/9)
    - January-June 1945 (Box-folder 17/10)
    - July-December 1945 (Box-folder 17/11)
    - January-June 1946 (Box-folder 18/1)
    - July-December 1946 (Box-folder 18/2)
    - January-July 1947 (Box-folder 18/3)
    - August-December 1947 (Box-folder 18/4)
    - January-June 1949 (Box-folder 18/5)
    - July-December 1949 (Box-folder 18/6)
    - January-June 1950 (Box-folder 18/7)
    - July-December 1950 (Box-folder 18/8)
    - January-March 1951 (Box-folder 19/1)
    - April-June 1951 (Box-folder 19/2)
    - July-October 1951 (Box-folder 19/3)
    - November-December 1951 (Box-folder 19/4)
    - January-April 1952 (Box-folder 19/5)
    - May-December 1952 (Box-folder 19/6)
    - January-December 1953 (Box-folder 19/7)
    - January-April 1954 (Box-folder 19/8)
    - May-July 1954 (Box-folder 19/9)
    - August-December 1954 (Box-folder 19/10)
    - January-April 1955 (Box-folder 19/11)
    - May-July 1955 (Box-folder 19/12)
    - August-December 1955 (Box-folder 19/13)
    - January-April 1956 (Box-folder 20/1)
    - May-August 1956 (Box-folder 20/2)
    - August-December 1956 (Box-folder 20/3)
    - 1957 (Box-folder 20/4)
    - 1958 (Box-folder 20/5)
    - January-June 1959 (Box-folder 20/6)
    - July-December 1959 (Box-folder 20/7)
    - January-June 1960 (Box-folder 21/1)
    - July-December 1960 (Box-folder 21/2)
    - January-December 1961, January-June 1962 (Box-folder 21/3)
    - July-December 1962, 1963 (Box-folder 21/4)
    - 1964-1965 (Box-folder 21/5)
  - General Correspondence, 1936-1968; Subseries 4; 30.0 linear feet
    - A, 1936 (Box-folder 22/1)
    - F. E. Buck, 1936 (Box-folder 22/2)
    - B, 1936 (Box-folder 22/3)
    - C, 1936 (Box-folder 22/4)
    - D, 1936 (Box-folder 22/5)
    - E, 1936 (Box-folder 22/6)
    - F, 1936 (Box-folder 22/7)
    - G, 1936 (Box-folder 22/8)
    - H, 1936 (Box-folder 22/9)
    - I, 1936 (Box-folder 22/10)
    - J, 1936 (Box-folder 22/11)
    - K, 1936 (Box-folder 22/12)
    - L, 1936 (Box-folder 22/13)
    - M, 1936 (Box-folder 22/14)
    - N, 1936 (Box-folder 22/15)
    - P, 1936 (Box-folder 22/16)
    - R, 1936 (Box-folder 22/17)
    - S, 1936 (Box-folder 22/18)
    - T, 1936 (Box-folder 22/19)
    - U, 1936 (Box-folder 22/20)
    - V, 1936 (Box-folder 22/21)
    - W, 1936 (Box-folder 22/22)
    - Y, 1936 (Box-folder 22/23)
    - A, 1936 (Box-folder 23/1)
    - F. E. Buck, 1936 (Box-folder 23/2)
    - B, 1936 (Box-folder 23/3)
    - C, 1936 (Box-folder 23/4)
    - D, 1936 (Box-folder 23/5)
    - E, 1936 (Box-folder 23/6)
    - F, 1936 (Box-folder 23/7)
    - G, 1936 (Box-folder 23/8)
    - H, 1936 (Box-folder 23/9)
    - I, 1936 (Box-folder 23/10)
    - J, 1936 (Box-folder 23/11)
    - K, 1936 (Box-folder 24/1)
    - Levin Brothers, 1936 (Box-folder 24/2)
    - L, 1936 (Box-folder 24/3)
    - Mohawk Carpet Mills, 1936 (Box-folder 24/4)
    - Mohawk Carpet Mills, 1936 (Box-folder 24/5)
    - M, 1936 (Box-folder 24/6)
    - N, 1936 (Box-folder 24/7)
    - O, 1936 (Box-folder 24/8)
    - P, 1936 (Box-folder 24/9)
    - Q, 1936 (Box-folder 25/1)
    - R, 1936 (Box-folder 25/2)
    - Salisbury and Satterlee, 1936 (Box-folder 25/3)
    - S, 1936 (Box-folder 25/4)
    - T, 1936 (Box-folder 25/5)
    - U, 1936 (Box-folder 25/6)
    - V, 1936 (Box-folder 25/7)
    - W, 1936 (Box-folder 25/8)
    - Y, 1936 (Box-folder 25/9)
    - A, 1937 (Box-folder 25/10)
    - F. E. Buck, 1937 (Box-folder 25/11)
    - B, 1937 (Box-folder 25/12)
    - C, 1937 (Box-folder 25/13)
    - D, 1937 (Box-folder 25/14)
    - E, 1937 (Box-folder 25/15)
    - F, 1937 (Box-folder 25/16)
    - G, 1937 (Box-folder 25/17)
    - H, 1937 (Box-folder 25/18)
    - I, 1937 (Box-folder 26/1)
    - J, 1937 (Box-folder 26/2)
    - K, 1937 (Box-folder 26/3)
    - Levin Brothers, 1937 (Box-folder 26/4)
    - L, 1937 (Box-folder 26/5)
    - Mohawk Carpet Mills, 1937 (Box-folder 26/6)
    - M, 1937 (Box-folder 26/7)
    - National Retail Furniture Association, 1937 (Box-folder 26/8)
    - N, 1937 (Box-folder 26/9)
    - O, 1937 (Box-folder 26/10)
    - P, 1937 (Box-folder 26/11)
    - R, 1937 (Box-folder 26/12)
    - Salisbury and Satterlee, 1937 (Box-folder 26/13)
    - S, 1937 (Box-folder 26/14)
    - T, 1937 (Box-folder 27/1)
    - U, 1937 (Box-folder 27/2)
    - V, 1937 (Box-folder 27/3)
    - W, 1937 (Box-folder 27/4)
    - Y, 1937 (Box-folder 27/5)
    - Z, 1937 (Box-folder 27/6)
    - A, 1938 (Box-folder 27/7)
    - F. E. Buck, 1938 (Box-folder 27/8)
    - B, 1938 (Box-folder 27/9)
    - C, 1938 (Box-folder 27/10)
    - C, 1938 (Box-folder 27/11)
    - D, 1938 (Box-folder 27/12)
    - E, 1938 (Box-folder 27/13)
    - F, 1938 (Box-folder 27/14)
    - G, 1938 (Box-folder 28/1)
    - H, 1938 (Box-folder 28/2)
    - I, 1938 (Box-folder 28/3)
    - J, 1938 (Box-folder 28/4)
    - K, 1938 (Box-folder 28/5)
    - Levin Brothers, 1938 (Box-folder 28/6)
    - L, 1938 (Box-folder 28/7)
    - Mohawk Carpet Mills, 1938 (Box-folder 28/8)
    - James E. Murray, 1938 (Box-folder 28/9)
    - M, 1938 (Box-folder 28/10)
    - National Retail Furniture Association, 1938 (Box-folder 28/11)
    - N, 1938 (Box-folder 28/12)
    - O, 1938 (Box-folder 28/13)
    - P, 1938 (Box-folder 28/14)
    - R, 1938 (Box-folder 28/15)
    - Salisbury and Satterlee, 1938 (Box-folder 28/16)
    - S, 1938 (Box-folder 29/1)
    - T, 1938 (Box-folder 29/2)
    - U, 1938 (Box-folder 29/3)
    - V, 1938 (Box-folder 29/4)
    - W, 1938 (Box-folder 29/5)
    - Z, 1938 (Box-folder 29/6)
    - A, 1939 (Box-folder 29/7)
    - F. E. Buck, 1939 (Box-folder 29/8)
    - B, 1939 (Box-folder 29/9)
    - C, 1939 (Box-folder 29/10)
    - C, 1939 (Box-folder 29/11)
    - D, 1939 (Box-folder 29/12)
    - E, 1939 (Box-folder 29/13)
    - F, 1939 (Box-folder 30/1)
    - G, 1939 (Box-folder 30/2)
    - H, 1939 (Box-folder 30/3)
    - I, 1939 (Box-folder 30/4)
    - J, 1939 (Box-folder 30/5)